Well then, I'll use that one.
じゃあね、そいつをね、使っていくからね
That's really bad, really.
そいつやばいんだよ、本当に
Because it's really amazing.
本当にすごいから
What's wrong?
何がやばいかって
Well, I have a little request for this.
これはね、ちょっとリクエストがあって、
I thought I'd give it a try.
やっていこうかなと思ったんですよ
Because it's amazing.
すごいから
Huh?
あれ?
Light
光
Are you saying?
ってる?
It's here.
来 たよ
This is amazing.
すごいの来たよ、これ
where?
どこ?
It looks amazing.
すごい映ってる
Ah, it's here.
あ、来た
This is amazing.
すごいよ、これ
You can see it, right?
映ってるでしょ?
It's reflected.
映ってる
This is amazing.
すごいね、これね
It's fine just to do that.
すだけでいいけど
Well, it gets blurry.
まあ、ぼやけちゃうね
Maybe it's nearby.
それは近くであると多分
Well then, let's take a look.
じゃあ、ちょっと見ていこうかな
No.
いやだ
Amazing, amazing.
すごい、すごい
This is terrible.
やばい、これ
It's going to be amazing.
すごいことになってる
Can't you see it?
見えんな?
I don't think you can see it.
見えなさそうじゃな
Awesome.
すげえ
It may not be visible.
見えないかもしれない
I want to see it.
見たい
Well, it's stopped somehow.
あれ、なんか止まってるか
picture?
え?
why?
なんで?
picture?
え?
I can't see it.
すげえ見えない
This is difficult.
むずいな、これ
Quite tight.
かなりきつい
I can't see it at all.
全然見えないよ
Normally.
普通に
I don't know what it is though.
何が何だか分かんないんだけど
Do you understand?
分かる?
I don't know.
分かんない
You can't see it at all.
全然見えないじゃん
Don't you want to say it?
言いたくない?
Yeah.
うん
Before, that's fine.
前じゃあ、結構
It was quite painful to open it.
結構、開けたの痛かったのかなり
It hurt.
痛かったよ
I said it hurts, it hurts.
痛い、痛いって言ったけど
Ah, but you might be able to see it.
あ、でも見えるかも
I'll take it a little deeper.
もうちょい奥させるよ
What?
何の?
This one is a little more on the cunt side.
これ、もうちょっとおまんこの方に寄せられてる
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
Ah, nice.
あ、いいね
Ah, I can see it.
あ、見えそう
Your pussy is so small.
おまんこちっちゃいな
It's so tiny.
すげえちっちゃい
Hey, I have to delete my thoughts.
ちょっと、 思考削除しないとダメだな
Try putting it in your pussy.
お ま んこ入れてみて
Yeah.
うん
Oh yeah, try putting it in.
そうそうそう、入れてみて
There's nothing showing.
何も映ってないね
Oh, that's inside your pussy.
お、それ、おまんこの中
Look.
ほら
Ah, that's on the right.
あ、それ右にあるじゃん
That was stuck earlier.
あれが挟まってたの、さっき
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
Up, up, up.
上、上、上
Up, up, up, up.
上、上、上、上
That's probably why it hurt.
だから 痛かったんだよ、多分
Look, it's on the top right now.
ほら、右上にあるじゃん、今
Look, look, look.
ほら、ほら、ほら
It hurt because it was stuck.
あれが挟まってたから痛かったの
The one around there.
あの辺のやつ
Do you understand?
わかる?
Look, it's there on the top right.
右上に、ほら、あるじゃん
Look, I'm about to get stuck right now.
ほら、今挟まりそう
No, no, no.
やだ、やだ、やだ
No, it's okay now, I'm holding it down.
いや、今大丈夫、押さえてるから
Ah, that's amazing, but you can see it.
あ、すげえ、でも見えるっちゃ見えるんだね
I can see it, I can see it.
見えるっちゃ見える
But, well, a bit of thinking and error is required.
けど、 まあ、ちょっと思考錯誤が必要なんで、
Let's do it again, then.
またやっていこうか、じゃあ
feeling
気持
Is it okay?
ち いい?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Can I say it out loud?
声出していい?
Don't hold back.
我慢しないでね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Okay.
よし
Now let's go home, let's go in.
これでもう家に行こう、入るよ
Okay, let's go.
よし、行くよ
よし、 行 くよ
why?
なんで?
Because my pussy spread.
おまんこ広がったから
I'll come in.
入るよ
I'll say it earlier.
さっき言うよ
I'll just tell you, okay?
さっき言うよ、大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
Okay, then, can I do this for a second?
じゃあ、じゃあ、これさ、 ちょっとやっていい?
By yourself?
自分で?
Yeah.
うん
Give me a little help.
ちょっとお手掛けしてくれ
Will you help me?
お手掛けしてくれるの?
Give it a try, that's it.
ちょっとやってみて、それで
It's a pleasant place.
気持ちいい場所ね
In my own way.
自分なりに
Do it for yourself.
自分にしてくれね
Yeah.
うん
Is it wrong to do it myself?
自分でやるとダメなの?
Don't you feel comfortable doing it yourself?
自分でやると気持しくないの?
It's okay, no.
大丈夫、ない
Does it feel better to stay stuck in the mud?
泥止まった方が気持ちいいの?
already?
もう?
There's a little bit in there.
少し入ってる
Wow, that's amazing.
は ー、すげー
That's amazing.
すごいよ
Kyunto.
きゅんと
I couldn't get it out.
抜けなくなっちゃった
Let's keep walking.
このまま歩こう
I can't get out.
抜けない
I can't get rid of it anymore.
もう抜けなくなっちゃった
What should I do?
どうしよう
It slipped out.
抜けた
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
That's amazing.
すごいね
I'll come in.
入るよ
Does your dick fit in?
おちんぽ入る?
Let's put it in
入れちゃお
cormorant?
う?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそう そう
Enter, enter.
入る入る
It's in, it's in.
入 ってる入ってる
Is it in?
入ってる?
It's in.
入ってるよ
That's amazing.
すごいよ
It's in.
入ってるよ
There's a dick in it.
おちんぽ入ってるよ
Ah, I'm in.
あ、入った
Try moving.
動いてみ
Please be careful.
気をしてみて
Isn't it hard?
固いでしょ?
Hard.
固い
Wait.
待ってね
Let's move.
動いてみよ
A place that feels good.
気持ちいいところを
That's amazing.
すごいよ
Look.
ほら
Try moving.
動いてみて
Because it's spinning.
回ってるから
It's in.
入ってる
nice.
いいね
Isn't it hard?
固いでしょ?
Dick.
おちんぽ
It's hard.
固いよ
copper?
どう?
Something goes in.
なんか入る
Look, it's in.
ほら、入ってる
There's a lot in it.
すごい入ってるよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
No.
いやね
This is amazing.
すごいこれ
It's so erotic.
すごいエロい
You took it off.
脱がせたね
picture?
え?
You made me take it off.
脱がせられたね
Did you see it?
見た?
This pants.
このパンツ
Tiger.
タイガー
Do you like Tiger?
タイガーが好きなの?
Because it's tiger pants.
タイガーパンツだからですよ
It goes well with the uniform, right?
制服に合うでしょ?
This color.
この色
Will it fit?
合うかな?
It fits perfectly.
めっちゃ合ってるよ
My dick will come out.
おちんぽ出てくるよ
Does a real, real penis feel better?
本当のリアルのちんぽの方が気持ちいいかな?
picture?
え?
Does a real penis feel better?
リアルちんちんの方が気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
tight.
きつい
Ah, okay.
あ、いいよ
give.
あげる
I'll give it to you.
あげるよ
thank you.
ありがとう
It's no good if it's covered.
かぶった状態でダメよ
first.
最初
Do you watch it all the time?
ずっと見る?
Yeah.
うん
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってきたね
Yeah.
うん
Oh, good.
お、いい
cute.
かわいい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいもん
Two more.
もう2本
Yeah.
うん
Yeah yeah yeah.
うん うんうん
lie?
嘘?
Do you only see this far?
ここまでしか見ないの?
Yeah.
うん
a?
あ?
ice cream.
アイスクリーム
This is ice cream.
これアイスな
good.
いい
Okay, let's chat.
よし、じゃべっていこうか